长官
Sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
家火一号  我是阔土  能收到吗
Home Fire 1, this is Open Range, do you copy?
收到  阔土
Copy, Open Range.
情况怎样
Status?
目标已占领  哥们
Location secured, brother.
非常好
Fantastic.
货物呢
The shipment?
我们正在逐层搜索
We're searching floor by floor.
这里的居民不是...很配合
The residents haven't been... very cooperative.
我真惊讶
I'm surprised.
这些人都退化成什么玩意儿了
These people have regressed into God knows what.
简直就像不识好歹的老鼠一样气人
It's like getting mad at a rat that can't tell right from wrong.
嗯  让他们尝尝法律与秩序的滋味
Yeah, well, the small taste of some law and order
他们就知道好歹了
will help them remember.
那当然
It sure will.
随时汇报
Keep me posted.
收到
Copy.
长官
Sir.
怎么了
What?
我们有两个人在东出口被干掉了
We've got two down at the east exit.
三层
不
No! No, no!
不要
Please, god, no!
求你了  不要
Please! Don't, don't, don't!
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十四集
联邦警察三局
达里尔
Daryl.
我刚还找你呢
Was just looking for you.
是吗
Yeah?
我最近一直在忙兼职
Been doing a little more of the side thing lately.
有家里的消息吗
Anything else about home?
-没有  但是...  -迪克森
- Not exactly, but  - Dixon.
你今天还来吧
You joining us today?
嗯
Yeah.
过会儿一起吃午饭吧
You want to have lunch later?
好  中午餐厅见
Yeah. Noon at the diner?
一言为定
It's a date.
好
Okay.
怎么了
What?
你真符合警察的刻板印象
Just really living up to that stereotype.
我以前就喜欢吃
I mean, I liked 'em before.
要吗
No? Mm.
早上好
Good morning.
今天的任务分配如下
Today's duty assignments are as follows --
道格拉斯和罗斯  A区
Douglas and Ross, Sector A.
利姆和贝克  B区
Lim and Baker, you're B.
麦克休和豪厄尔  C区
McHugh and Howell, take C.
埃斯皮诺萨和迪克森  你们去D区
And Espinosa and Dixon, I want you on Sector D.
有问题吗
Any questions?
好  去干活吧
Alright, let's get to it.
如果你只是盯着牙齿
If you're just staring at those teeth.
呆呆地站着  那就完蛋了
and you're just freezing up, I mean it's over.
大部分人的问题是
You see, the problem that most people have
他们会惊慌失措
is when they start to panic.
但我在腐尸旁可是心如止水
But when I'm around the rotters, my heart rate actually goes down.
迪克森看到过
Dixon's seen it.
看到什么
Seen what?
我是怎么对付腐尸的  说吧
How I handle myself with the rotters. Come on.
对对对
Oh, yeah, yeah.
可有意思了
It's, uh -- It's good stuff.
迪克森  埃斯皮诺萨
Hey, Dixon, Espinosa...
什么事
What's up?
北边界附近发现了尸群
Swarm's been spotted near the north perimeter.
我们被派去调查
We've been assigned to check it out.
但维克说我们只负责巡逻
But Vicker says we only work patrol.
对  她现在想看看
Yeah, and now she wants to see
你们在墙外表现如何
what you can do outside the walls.
你们的区有人去了  我们走吧
Look, your sector's covered, so let's go.
快点
Come on!
再走一步  你就会死
One more step, you die.
放下武器
Drop your weapons.
你先放下
You first.
不可能
Not happening.
我们是来帮忙的
We're here to help.
你们是谁
And who the hell are you?
-我是...  -她是玛姬
- I'm -- - Her name is Maggie.
天啊
Jesus.
各位
Everybody.
咱们先把家伙收进裤子里吧
Let's put our shit back in our pants and zip up.
好吗
Shall we?
孩子
Hey, kiddo.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我们住在这里
We live here.
好  那现在怎么办
Okay. So what now?
他们抓住了加百利
They have Gabriel.
不  他们没有
No, they don't.
来吧
Come on.
伊恩  他用墙封住了门  以隐藏公寓
Ian -- he walled up the doors to hide the apartment.
这栋楼里有几间这种公寓
There's a couple in the building.
玛姬
Maggie?
我不确定你是否还活着
I wasn't sure you'd made it.
我差点就死了
I almost didn't.
你们偷了他们的枪
Did your people steal their guns?
-劫了那支车队吗  -没有
- Hijack their convoy? - No.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我受够了他们问我这个问题
I am really sick of them asking me this.
我也是
So am I.
你们怎么不有点种
You know, why don't you just ball up
别再含糊其辞  直接叫她骗子呢
and stop tiptoeing around it and call her a liar.
你们老大的书架上有头骨
Your boss had skulls on his bookcase,
所以没错  我觉得这是扯谎
so, yeah, I'm inclined to call bullshit.
-不是我们做的  -是吗  那是谁做的
- We didn't do it. - Yeah? Then who did?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
我们必须救他们出去
We have to get these people out of here.
我们不能走
We can't leave.
不能丢下仍在躲藏的同胞
Not with the rest of my people still hiding.
好吧  你想做什么
Okay. What do you want to do?
分成小队
Split into teams,
找到每层活下来的人
sweep each floor for whoever's left,
一起找条路出去
then find a way out together.
好
Okay.
好  走吧
Alright, let's go.
你留下
You stay here.
他们需要信任的人来保护他们
They need someone they trust protecting them.
她跟我走
She comes with me.
还有多远
How much longer?
不远了
Oh, not long.
就在那里
There it is.
其他人呢
Where's everybody else?
没其他人了
There is no one else.
你要我们四个人干掉那么多行尸吗
You want the four of us to take all that out?
你们不用干掉它们
You aren't gonna take them out.
你们要穿过它们
You're gonna go through them.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我在说我的朋友库珀
I'm talking about my buddy Cooper.
我们从小一起长大
We grew up together.
他住在一座大房子里  就在那里
He lived in a big house -- right -- right down there.
他爸爸是SDS银行的主席
His dad was actually the president of SDS Bank.
总之  他爸爸也是个末日准备者
Anyway, his dad was also a prepper,
所以他把办公室改造成了安全屋
so he turned his office into a panic room.
他把好东西都藏在那里
It's where he kept all his good shit,
比如威士忌  大麻  摇头丸  可卡因
like whiskey, weed, E, coke.
他也把现金藏在那里
He also kept cash in there.
一大笔现金
Lots of it.
那就是我要你们去取的东西
And that is what I need you to get for me.
这是个玩笑  对吧
This is a joke, right?
不  亲爱的  不是
No, sweetie, it isn't.
好吧  我那个泼妇老妈
Alright, look, my bitch mother
取消了我的信用额度
has cut off my line of credit,
所以我需要用一些有创意的方法
so I need to come up with creative ways to...
来维持我的生活方式
support my lifestyle.
让这些混蛋去做吧
So have these dickheads do it.
他们不想去  因为他们不能在那里开枪
They don't want to because they can't shoot down there.
射出去的子弹要登记
You see, fired rounds are tracked,
所以会引起疑问
so it'd raise questions.
如果他们不能开枪
And if these guys can't shoot guns, well,
他们很可能会被行尸围死
they would probably get dog-piled and suffocate.
但你们两位
But you two?
我知道你们能做到
I know that you can do it.
我相信你们
I -- I believe in you.
这是办公室电子锁的密码
Now, this is the code to the office's electric lock.
车库里有一台太阳能发电机
Now, there's a solar generator in the garage
-你们可以去...  -不
- that you can go thro-- - Nah.
我们不去
No, we ain't doing it.
你们要去
Yes, you are.
你们给身上涂上血
Now, you're gonna slime yourself up with guts,
然后穿过那个尸群
and then you are gonna walk through that swarm,
给我把钱拿回来
and you are gonna get me my cash.
不然呢
Or what?
你们的孩子还好吗
Hey, how are your kids doing?
那个小子  他刚跳了两级  对吧
Your little one, he just jumped two grades, right?
可可会走路了吗
And -- And Coco, is she walking yet?
你认为"高级军事训练"
You think your "Advanced military training's"
现在能帮到你吗
gonna help you right now?
放下  不然你俩都得死
Drop it, or you're both dead!
我会先爆了这个混蛋的头
Not before I take this asshole's head off.
我们说清楚一件事
Let's get something a little straight.
你再敢威胁我们的孩子一次
You threaten our kids one more time,
我就会把你开膛破肚...
and I will gut you --
谁说要伤害小孩子了
Hey, who said anything about hurting kids?
我只是在说  我能让他们过得更好
I'm just saying that I can make their life easier.
或者你动手  让他们变成孤儿
Or you can make them both orphans.
由你决定
It's your call.
做了这件事就完了吗
We do this, and that's it?
对
Yeah.
那肯定
Totally.
血迹  是新的
Blood -- it's fresh.
这边
This way.
这里
Over here.
这锁需要通电
You need power for the lock.
你背后
Hey, behind you.
他们尸变的时间不超过几天
Can't be more than a few days since they've turned.
是的
Yeah.
有人吗
Hello?
你们是另一队人吗
Are you with another group?!
我们是联邦军
We're with The Commonwealth Army.
天啊  真抱歉
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
钱在里面  但是
The money is in here, but I'm --
只剩下我一个人了
I'm the only one who's left.
他以前就做过这事
He's done this before.
求你们了  别丢下我
Please, please! Please don't leave me!
-不  -别丢下我
- No, no. - Don't leave me!
我在里面待了好久  求求了
I've been in here so long! Please!
不  我们不会丢下你
No, no, no. We won't.
我们和派你来的人不是一伙的
We're not with the people who sent you in.
是他们强迫你来的吗
Did they force you in here?
我有债务  有一天
I was in debt, and then, uh, one day,
有人来我家找我
a man showed up at my door,
他说他能帮我摆脱债务
and he said he could get me get out of it.
我有两个孩子
I have two kids.
-没事了  -求你们了
- It's okay, it's okay. Where -- - Please!
你们当时来了多少人
How many of you were sent in?
十二个人
12 of us.
但只有三个人进了房子
But only three of us made it inside.
我们启动了发电机  然后
We got the generators on, and then -- and then,
跟我一起的两个人  他们内讧了
the two guys that I was with, they turned on each other.
所以我把他们锁在了门外
So I locked them out, and that's --
然后就没电了
that's when the power went off,
我一直打不开这扇门
and I-I haven't been to get this door open!
你陪着她  我去找发电机
You stay with her. I'll go find the generator.
没关系的  挺住  好吗
It's alright. Just hang on, okay?
好
Okay.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫爱普尔
My name's April.
我叫罗西塔
I'm Rosita.
罗西塔
Rosita.
你不要担心
Listen, I don't want you to worry.
我们会成功的  好吗
We're gonna make this work, okay?
你没说一句话就走了
You left without saying a word.
我走是因为我在乎
I left because I gave a shit.
我走是因为大家需要我走
I left because that's what everyone needed.
对吧
Right?
然后你找到了他们
And you find them?
她是你的什么人
And your -- what is she to you?
你结婚了
You're married?
很疯狂吧
It's crazy, right?
你适合这里
You being here fits.
伊恩书架上的头骨也有你的一份功劳吧
You have a hand in putting any of those skulls on Ian's shelf?
带着盖世太保来的人还好意思说这话
Says the guy that rolled up with the Gestapo.
我们不知情
We didn't know.
我们现在住的地方
The place we're living now is
与我们所见过的任何地方都不同
different from any place we've ever seen.
并没有不同
No, it isn't.
我希望是不同  但是
I hoped that they might be, but...
他们只想吞并其他社区
they just want to swallow up other communities.
他们与低语者一样
They're like the Whisperers.
只不过戴着不同面具
They just wear different masks.
尼根  收到了吗
Negan, do you copy?
嗯  你在哪
Yeah. Where are you?
五层
Fifth floor.
听着  士兵分散了
Listen, the soldiers are spread out,
但时间不多
but our window's closing.
让大家动起来
Tell the others to move.
收到
Copy that.
玛姬还和你在一起吗
Hey, is Maggie still with you?
是的
She is.
好  我只是...
Alright, look. It's just, um...
别担心了
Stop worrying.
很快见
I'll see you soon.
糟了
Oh, shit.
坐下别动
Sit and stay!
中士
Sarge,
我在外围发现了一辆皮卡
I found a truck on the perimeter.
里面藏着一个孩子
Kid hiding inside.
-你是说有个孩子吗  -是的
- Did you say a kid? - Affirmative.
生姜
Ginger?
我怀孕差不多十二周了
I'm 12 weeks, give or take.
对  是他的孩子
And yeah, it's his.
他不希望我告诉你
Not that he'd want me telling you.
安妮  你在吗
Hey, Annie, do you copy?
我在
I'm here.
我发现了一个人
I found someone.
谁
Who?
玛姬的儿子
Maggie's son.
什么
What?!
是的
Yeah.
看来你不知道自己还带了个偷渡者
Turns out you had stowaway that you didn't know about.
我去找你
I'm coming to you.
不  你和安妮待在一起
No. You stay with Annie.
尼根
Negan --
他很安全  好吗
He's safe. Alright?
你别分心
You stay focused.
如果他有什么不测...
If anything happens to him...
有我帮他挡着呢
It'll have to happen to me first.
他会照顾好他
He's in good hands.
他是杀了他父亲的人
He's in the hands of the man who killed his father.
我知道他是什么人
I know who he is.
他做过什么
And what he did.
他告诉我了
He told me.
而你仍然和他在一起
And you're still with him?
我们的手都不干净
None of us have clean hands.
我见过人们为了生存会对彼此做什么
I've seen what people will do to each other to survive.
有时候  他们对我做过
Sometimes, it was done to me.
有时候  我也对他们做过
Other times, I did it to them.
我不以此为荣  但这确实发生了
I'm not proud of it, but it happened.
现在我只能努力变得更好
All I can do now is try to be better.
就像他一样
Just like him.
他没资格忘记
He doesn't get to forget.
他没忘
He hasn't.
我在乎的是他现在是什么人
What matters to me is who he is now.
他是一个会尽一切努力保护你儿子的人
He's someone who'll do whatever he can to protect your boy.
我妈妈让我离你远点
My mom told me to stay away from you.
你妈妈是个很聪明的女士
Well, your mom is a very smart lady.
她为什么不喜欢你
Why doesn't she like you?
因为很久以前发生过的一件事
Because of something that happened a long time ago.
是坏事吗
Was it something bad?
是的
Yeah.
是的  是坏事
Yeah, it was, uh -- it was something bad.
你是坏人吗
Are you a bad man?
我曾是
I was.
孩子  我...
Look, kid, I --
我妈妈说坏人杀了我爸爸
My mom told me a bad man killed my dad.
就是你  对吧
It was you, wasn't it?
对
Yeah.
对  是我
Yeah, it was me.
听着
Look...
孩子  我从你和你妈妈那里夺走的东西
Kid, what I took away from you and your mom,
不管我说什么或做什么
there is nothing I can say or do
都不可能弥补这件事
that is gonna make that better.
我知道你想扣下扳机
And I know you want to pull that trigger,
我不怪你
and I don't blame you.
问题是  如果你扣了
The thing is, if you do,
坏人就会知道我们藏在这里
the bad people are gonna know where we're hiding.
也许我该死  因为我对你爸爸做的事
Maybe I deserve to die for what I did to your dad,
对你家人做的事
to your family...
但这里的人们
...but these people here...
他们不该死
they don't.
爱普尔  你还在吗
April, are you still with me?
在
Yes.
好  我们要进去了
Alright, we're coming in.
天啊
Oh, God.
谢谢
Thank you! Thank you!
-好了  -谢谢
- Okay, okay. - Thank you!
保险箱在那里
The safe is right there.
-能打开吗  -不知道  试试吧
- Can you get into it? - I don't know. We'll try.
什么声音
What is that?
该死
Aw, shit.
不
No!  No, no, no!
不  它们会被引进屋的
No, they're drawn inside the house!
-好的  -关掉
- Okay, alright! - Shut it off!
好  只要切断电路板的电源就行
Yeah, I just have to cut the power to the circuit board.
快点  快点
Hurry. Hurry! Hurry!
快点
Hurry!
Come on.
过来  帮帮我
Come here! Give me a hand!
它们来了  快点
Oh, they're coming! Please, hurry!
我知道
I know!
求你们快点
Hurry, please!
走吧
Come on.
离门远点
Move away from the door.
我们从原路回去
We go out the same way we came in.
-动作别太大  我们直接从门口走出来  -好
- No sudden moves. We walk right out that door. - Okay.
-准备好了吗  -等等
- You ready? - Wait.
她身上没有足够的血
She doesn't have enough blood on her.
天啊  不
Oh, God. No.
-穿上  -你怎么办
- Put that on. - What about you?
我没事
I'll be fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
还让不让我们进来了
You gonna let us in or what?
你怎么知道我们在这里
How'd you know where we were?
你没来吃午餐  所以我叫上了默瑟
You didn't show up for lunch, so I got Mercer.
阿尔维斯和卡塞尔说你们进来偷钱了
Alves and Castle said you came here to steal some money.
不是
Nope.
不是这样的
That did not happen.
你们现在开始打家劫舍了吗
What, y'all looting houses now? Is that it?
是塞巴斯蒂安逼我们进来的
Sebastian made us come in here.
他用孩子威胁我们
He threatened our kids.
你又是哪位
And who are you?
一些士兵把我们带到这里
Some soldiers brought a group of us here,
他们说
and they told us that if we --
我们进来就能分一笔钱
we got in, we could have a cut of the money.
你们当时有多少人
How many were in your group?
十二个人  现在只剩我了
12. Now it's just me.
还剩多少发子弹
How many more rounds we got?
大概十发
Maybe 10.
外面的行尸可不止这个数
Lot more walkers out there than that.
我们涂上血  然后走
We gut up, and we go.
不
No! No! No!
不  求你了
No! No, please!
不不不  求你了
No! No, no! No, no, no, please!
好了
Alright.
这些人啊
These people...
找到人以后  只要问不出有用信息
Anyone you find, they refuse to give you something useful,
就直接爆头  然后继续前进
you just pop them in the head and move on.
下个小时内找不到枪
We find our guns in the next hour
就将这里烧成灰烬
or we burn this place to the ground.
加百利  亚伦  在吗
Gabriel, Aaron, you there?
在
We're here.
-伊莱哲也在吗  -他在
- Is Elijah with you? - He is.
很好  我有个计划
Good. I have a plan.
有发现吗
Anything?
没有  长官
Nothing, sir.
亚伦  去屋顶
Aaron, up to the roof!
又是那个该死的神父  快走
It's that goddamn priest again. Let's go!
停下
Stop!
放下枪
Drop it!
我真他妈受够了
Just enough of this shit!
你在想什么啊
What are you even thinking?
背叛我  背叛联邦
Just turning on me? On The Commonwealth?
为了什么
For what?
某个廉租房军阀和他的小偷马仔吗
Some tenement warlord and all these thieving followers?
我真以为你更聪明的
I just -- I really thought you were smarter than all that.
所有士兵  立刻上屋顶
All Troopers, up to the roof, now!
指挥官需要支援
Commander needs assistance!
长官  我们遭遇了敌人
Sir, we have combatants inbound.
撤退
Fall back!
好了
Okay.
真不错
That's good.
懂得分辨的智慧  对吧
The wisdom to know the difference, right?
听着  事情有点失控了
Look, things just got a little out of hand.
我们都需要...
We all just need to -- hoo! --
喘口气
take a breath, right?
听着
Listen.
听着  我们只需要谈谈
Listen, we just need to talk things --
天啊
Oh, God!
不
No!
天啊  不
Oh, God, no!
不
No! No!
救命  不
Help! No!
你们刚才要能帮忙就好了
Could've used your help back there.
嗯  看起来是这样
Yeah, looks like it.
但我们不听你的命令
But we don't answer to you.
这是钱吗
That the money?
你们之前还派过多少人去
How many others did you send in before them?
我不知道  三十个人
I don't know. What, 30?
或许四十个人吧
Maybe 40?
至少我们没空手回去
Hey, at least we're coming home with --
你们必须把钱给他
You have to pay him.
-塞巴斯蒂安  -什么
- Sebastian.  - What?
-不  -如果不给他  他会报复你们的
- No -- - If you don't, he'll come after you,
你们斗不过他
and that's a fight you ain't gonna win.
我带包进门
I'll carry the bags through the gate.
他们不会搜我
They won't search me.
好
Alright.
他们在这里啊
There they are!
所以呢
So?
太好了
Yes!
好样的  女士们先生们
Well done, ladies and gents!
好样的
Well done!
真好
Yes!
他们哪去了
Hey, where are...?
阿尔维斯和卡塞尔呢
Where are Alves and Castle?
他们没能活下来
They didn't make it.
-那是什么  -你们的一份
- What's that? - That is your cut.
我当然会给你们钱了
I'm of course going to pay you.
天啊  恭喜  两位
Oh, my God -- congrats, guys!
我们做到了
We did it!
我真高兴我们又成朋友了
I am so glad that we're friends again.
阔土  收到了吗
Open Range, do you copy?
阔土
Open Range...
进
Yeah.
很晚了
It's late.
你去哪了
Where you been?
我去帮朋友脱困了
I was helping some friends out of a jam.
是吗
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
他们去为总管的儿子办事
They were on a -- a mission for the Governor's son.
他一直在找走投无路的人
He's been finding desperate people,
派他们穿过尸群  去取藏着的现金
sending them through swarms to get stashes of cash.
大部分人都没活下来
Most of them didn't make it out.
他派你的朋友们去做吗
He sent your friends to do this?
嗯
Yeah.
他们都活着回来了吧
They all made it back, though?
差点就死了
Barely.
好
Good.
钱呢
And the money?
他们拿到了吗
Did they get it?
拿到了
Yeah.
终于拿到了
Finally.
为什么要派其他人去
Why -- Why did you send the other people?
他们做了什么
W-What did they do?
他们让自己陷入了困境
They put themselves in bad situations,
要么是做了愚蠢的选择
either through stupid choices
要么是不愿意遵守规矩
or an unwillingness to play by the rules.
我这是想救他们一命
I tried to throw them a lifeline.
听着
Look...
这地方行得通是因为每个人都各司其职
this place works because everyone plays their part.
如果你做不到或不想做
If you can't or won't,
其他人都会被连累
it hurts everyone else.
体制就是这样崩溃的
That's when the system breaks down,
我们不能允许这种事发生
and we can't let that happen.
你懂我的意思吧
You know what I'm saying?
我懂
Yeah.
我懂  人要么成为问题
Yeah, people can either be part be of the problem
要么解决问题
or part of the solution.
我就知道你懂
I knew you'd get it.
那么
Well...
我不打扰你工作了
I'll let you get back to work.
-卡萝尔  -嗯
- Carol. - Yeah.
能和一个看得到大局的人交谈
It's nice to be able to talk to someone who...
真是太好了
sees the big picture.
没多少人能看到
Not many can.
你和我还有一些未完成的事
You and I, we have some unfinished business, don't we?
这样吧
I tell you what.
你先和妈妈回去
You go back with your mom.
帮她重建家园
Help her rebuild your home.
过几年  等你再长大一些
And in a few years, when you've grown up a bit...
来找我
...come find me.
我向你保证  我们会做个了结
And I promise you, we will settle it.
他对你说了什么
What did he say to you?
你们打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
不能回联邦了
Can't go back to Commonwealth.
不  我们必须回去
No, we kinda have to.
兰斯会想知道这里发生了什么
Lance is gonna want to know what happened here.
更迫切的问题是这些人
Well, the more immediate problem is these people.
霍恩斯比来找他们只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time before Hornsby comes for them.
那我们必须做些什么了
Then we have to do something.
这一切都是为了一些枪
All of this over some guns.
嗯  但如果伊恩没偷武器  那是谁偷的
Yeah, but if Ian didn't steal the weapons, who did?
两周前
不  不  求你了
No, no! Please, please, please, please!
不
No!
求你了  不
Please, no, no, no, please!
不  求你了
No, please, no, no!